[Home](https://isizulu.net/) · [Mobile](https://isizulu.net/m/) · [Usage](https://isizulu.net/usage/) · [Grammar](https://isizulu.net/grammar/) · [Pronunciation](https://isizulu.net/p11n/) · [About](https://isizulu.net/about/) · [Contact](https://isizulu.net/contact/) · [FAQ](https://isizulu.net/faq/) · [Forum](https://isizulu.net/forum/) · [Privacy](https://isizulu.net/pvc/)

Privacy Policy
--------------

This privacy policy is intended to inform the users of my website about the nature, scope and purpose of the collection and use of personal data by me, the website operator.

My website does not directly use or embed any external tools, services or content. Operators of websites to which I have linked receive your data (IP address, etc.) only when you (actively) click on the link I have set. Thus, you decide for yourself whether and with whom you want to share your data.

### Collection and processing of personal data, type and purpose of use

#### Using the website

When you visit my website, or use its OpenSearch interface or its API, your web browser automatically transmits certain information to the server, which could in turn make you identifiable. For example, your web browser transmits the IP address assigned by your provider. To provide the service, the web server processes the following information and stores it in a logfile:

* The [IP address](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IP_address) of the requesting computer, e.g.: **51.195.149.220**
* The API username if applicable, e.g.: **johndoe**
* The date and time of the request, e.g.: **28/Jun/2024:20:42:00**
* The HTTP request [method](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hypertext_Transfer_Protocol#Request_methods), e.g.: **GET**
* The requested [URL path](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/URL#Syntax), e.g.: **/pvc/**
* The HTTP version used in the request, e.g.: **HTTP/1.1**
* The HTTP [status code](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hypertext_Transfer_Protocol#Status_codes), e.g.: **200**
* The number of bytes transmitted to your browser, e.g.: **5189**
* The requested [domain](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Domain_name), e.g.: **isizulu.net**
* The website from which the request originated ([Referrer](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_referer)), e.g.: **https://duckduckgo.com/**
* The browser used and, if applicable, the operating system of your computer ([user agent](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/User_agent)), e.g.:  
    **Mozilla/5.0 (X11; Linux x86\_64; rv:109.0) Gecko/20100101 Firefox/115.0**
* The [TLS version](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Transport_Layer_Security) and [cipher suite](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cipher_suite) used by your browser, e.g.:  
    **TLSv1.3-TLS\_CHACHA20\_POLY1305\_SHA256**
* The term(s) you looked up in the dictionary and corresponding search sugggestions, if applicable.

When you click the "hide phonetic spelling" checkbox, a cookie is exchanged between the server and your browser for the sole purpose of remembering this setting.

I use the aforementioned information for the following purposes:

* Ensuring secure and stable server operations
* Accumulated, anonymized access statistics
* Further administrative tasks like identification of orphaned links or configuration errors

The server logfiles are stored for up to 7 days. IP addresses and browser identifiers are anonymized after 1 day.

#### Using my contact address

For inquiries not covered by the forum I offer you the possibility to [contact](https://isizulu.net/contact/) me by encrypted e-mail. In doing so, the specification of a valid e-mail address is required so that I know from whom the request originates and to be able to answer it. Further information can be given voluntarily.

#### Using the forum

The forum is hosted and operated externally by Tapatalk and is subject to their privacy policy. No data is exchanged between this website and the forum.

### Data security and data processing

All data processing of this website takes place on my own server located in Germany. I have taken appropriate technical and organizational protective measures to make it very difficult for potential attackers to compromise the server.

When visiting this website, an encrypted connection is initiated via the common TLS (Transport Layer Security) protocol. The highest encryption level (cipher suite) supported by your browser is used. You can tell whether an individual page of my website is transmitted in encrypted form by the display of a key or lock symbol in the URL line or status bar of your browser.

* * *

Proudly made without Facebook, Google, Twitter and other data suckas.
